Experimental College Records UA044
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Course files, 1965 -- 2012; UA044.003; 22.8 Linear Feet
  - EXP 47S, Spring 1987: Literature of Resistance, Voices of Oppression, Audrey Epstein and Deirdre Burns, UA044.003.023.00039 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47F, Fall 1985/Spring 1986: Oppression: The Pychosocial Experience, Grace Ross, 1985 -- 1986; UA044.003.023.00040 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47F, Fall 1984: Inherently Unequal: Boston's Black Parents View Desegregation, Alifa Mahmoud and Hattie McKinnis, UA044.003.023.00041 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47F, Fall 1979/Fall 1980/Fall 1982 (EXP 48F, Fall 1983): Career Planning and Decision-Making, Joanne Hadlock, 1979 -- 1983; UA044.003.023.00042 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47F, Fall 1982: The Vietnam Decade: Themes in Military Sociology, Paul Camacho, UA044.003.023.00043 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47S, Spring 1981: Nonviolence: From J.F.K. to 2001, Pat Farren, UA044.003.023.00044 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47S, Spring 1978: Cancer, Philip Morrissey, UA044.003.023.00045 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47F, Fall 1971: Art and Science of Ballet, Daphne Lowell, UA044.003.023.00046 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47F, Fall 1970: Fundamentals of Photography, Julian Brown, UA044.003.023.00047 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47S, Spring 1970: Photography, William Humphreys, UA044.003.023.00048 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47S, Spring 1970: Photography, Allen Koenig, UA044.003.023.00049 (Box 23)
  - EXP 47F, Fall 1967/Fall 1969: Beginning and Intermediate Photography, Frank Siteman, 1970; UA044.003.023.00050 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48S, Spring 1989: Prisoner's Rights, Michelle Schaffer, UA044.003.023.00051 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48S, Spring 1988: Women and Poverty in the U.S., Katherine Gilbert, UA044.003.023.00052 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48F, Fall 1986: Conscientious Objection, Michael Hovey, UA044.003.023.00053 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48S, Spring 1986: Abortion: a Century of Controversy, Carmen Whalen, UA044.003.023.00054 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48S, Spring 1984: The Laws of War and Armed Conflict, Phillipe Sands, UA044.003.023.00055 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48S, Spring 1981: War and War Prevention, Stephen Van Evera, UA044.003.023.00056 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48S, Spring 1980: Anthropology and Film: a Visual Approach to Ethnographic Studies, Barry Dornfield, Tom Rankin, and Jean Segal, UA044.003.023.00057 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48S, Spring 1976: Lichens and Local Flora, Seth Ammerman, UA044.003.023.00058 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48F, Fall 1972: Drama of Communication, Dilip Gaonkar, UA044.003.023.00059 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48S, Spring 1972: Invitation to Rhetoric and Communication, Dilip Gaonkar, UA044.003.023.00060 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48F, Fall 1971: Movement and Dance Therapy, Griselda White, UA044.003.023.00061 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48S, Spring 1971: Afro-Cuban Dance, Linda Dawson, UA044.003.023.00062 (Box 23)
  - EXP 48S, Spring 1969: The Blues, Jim Nollman, UA044.003.023.00063 (Box 23)
  - EXP 49S, Spring 1991: Reduce, Reuse, Recycle: Beyond Waste Disposal, Mark Rossi and Gretchen McClain, UA044.003.023.00064 (Box 23)
  - EXP 49F, Fall 1986: Projection of Power: Human Rights and U.S. Foreign Policy Since Vietnam, James Meehan and William Schwartz, UA044.003.023.00065 (Box 23)
  - EXP 49S, Spring 1986: Refuge and Reaction, Daniel Kanstroom, UA044.003.023.00066 (Box 23)
  - EXP 49S, Spring 1981: There's a Science to Getting into Publishing, Cathryn Jakobson, UA044.003.023.00067 (Box 23)
  - EXP 50S, Spring 1980: Introduction to Film, Carol Van Valkenburgh, UA044.003.023.00068 (Box 23)
  - EXP 50S, Spring 1978: History of Film, Stephen Anker, UA044.003.023.00069 (Box 23)
  - EXP 51F, Fall 1986: Introduction to Mass Communication, Ronald Kertzner, UA044.003.023.00070 (Box 23)
    label on file indicates class as "EXP 51CF"
  - EXP 51F, Fall 1985: Introduction to Mass Communications, Ann Fryling, UA044.003.023.00071 (Box 23)
  - EXP 51F, Fall 1984: Introduction to Mass Communications, Ann Fryling, UA044.003.023.00072 (Box 23)
  - EXP 51F, Fall 1982/Fall 1983: Introduction to Mass Communications, Donald Fishman, 1982 -- 1983; UA044.003.023.00073 (Box 23)
  - EXP 51F, Fall 1979: Hitchcock, Gerald Peary, UA044.003.023.00074 (Box 23)
  - EXP 51F, Fall 1978: History of Film II, Steven Anker, UA044.003.023.00075 (Box 23)
  - EXP 51F, Fall 1977: Personal Filmmaking, Stephen Anker, UA044.003.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - EXP 51S, Spring 1976/Spring 1977: Basic TV Production, Bill Riley, Mary Allen, 1976 -- 1977; UA044.003.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - EXP 52F, Fall 1994: Music Video: Reading the Signs of Our Times, Lieba Goldman, UA044.003.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - EXP 52S, Spring 1986/Spring 1987: International Media, Sherman Teichman, 1986 -- 1987; UA044.003.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - EXP 52S, Spring 1986: Comparative Analysis/International Mass Media, Sherman Teichman, UA044.003.024.00005 (Box 24)
    label on file designates class as "EXP 52CS"
  - EXP 52S, Spring 1985: International Mass Media, John Kochevar, UA044.003.024.00006 (Box 24)
    label designates class as "EXP 52CS"
  - EXP 52S, Spring 1984: International Mass Media, Paul Jalbert, UA044.003.024.00007 (Box 24)
    label on folder designates class as "EXP 52CS" - also, the folder is empty
  - EXP 52S, Spring 1983: International Mass Media: a Comparative Perspective, Wallace Roberts, UA044.003.024.00008 (Box 24)
    label on folder designates class as "EXP 52CS"
  - EXP 52S, Spring 1982: American Short Stories and Film, Wolfgang McAninch-Runzi, UA044.003.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - EXP 52S, Spring 1979: The Western, Aaron Lipstadt, UA044.003.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - EXP 52S, Spring 1978: Documentary Filmmaking, Bestor Cram, UA044.003.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - EXP 52S, Spring 1976/Fall 1976: TV Commercials, Ken Bell, UA044.003.024.00012 (Box 24)
  - EXP 52S, Spring 1968: Metaphor and Sanity, William Cressman, UA044.003.024.00013 (Box 24)
  - EXP 53S, Spring 1989: Writing for the Mass Media, Marcie Hershman, UA044.003.024.00014 (Box 24)
    label on folder designates class as "EXP 53CS"
  - EXP 53F, Fall 1985: Writing of the Mass Media, John Brady, UA044.003.024.00015 (Box 24)
    label on file designates class as "EXP 53CF"
  - EXP 53F, Fall 1983: Writing for the Mass Media, Elaine Weiss, UA044.003.024.00016 (Box 24)
  - EXP 53S, Spring 1983: Writing for the Mass Media, Laurence Barton, UA044.003.024.00017 (Box 24)
  - EXP 53S, Spring 1980: Film Animation: Anyone Can Do It, Flip Johnson, UA044.003.024.00018 (Box 24)
  - EXP 53F, Fall 1976: Candid Camera to Cassavetes, Bestor Cram, UA044.003.024.00019 (Box 24)
  - EXP 54S, Spring 1984/Spring 1985/Spring 1986/Spring 1987: Legal and Ethical Issues in Broadcasting, Nancy Dietz, 1984 -- 1987; UA044.003.024.00020 (Box 24)
    label on folder designates class as "EXP 54CS"
  - EXP 54S, Spring 1979/Fall 1979: Journalism: the Daily Newspaper, Charlotte Berman, UA044.003.024.00021 (Box 24)
  - EXP 54S, Spring 1977: Super-8 Sound Film Making, Ken Bell and Bestor Cram, UA044.003.024.00022 (Box 24)
  - EXP 54F, Fall 1976: Exploring Video Workshop, Charlie Tesch, Jim Jones, Stephen Guy, Mary Tisso, Terry Signaigo, Bob Matorin, Irwin Friman, Barry McQuilken, and Greg Hill, UA044.003.024.00023 (Box 24)
  - EXP 54S, Spring 1976: Media Insight, Steve Robinson, UA044.003.024.00024 (Box 24)
  - EXP 54S, Spring 1976: The Plains Indians, Marion Haas, 1971; UA044.003.024.00025 (Box 24)
  - EXP 55S, Spring 1987: Novels into Film, Ingeborg Fulepp, UA044.003.024.00026 (Box 24)
  - EXP 55F, Fall 1986/Fall 1993: Effective Public Speaking, Edward McCarthy, 1986 -- 1993; UA044.003.024.00027 (Box 24)
  - EXP 55S, Spring 1986: Cinema and the Real, Barry Dornfeld, UA044.003.024.00028 (Box 24)
  - EXP 55S, Spring 1985: Introduction to Mass Media Newsrooms, Carla Roudabush, UA044.003.024.00029 (Box 24)
  - EXP 55S, Spring 1984/Fall 1984: Community Media Production, Rob Goldman, Sharon Donahue, and John Kusiak, UA044.003.024.00030 (Box 24)
  - EXP 55F, Fall 1983: Communications and the Future, Randolph Steer, UA044.003.024.00031 (Box 24)
  - EXP 55S, Spring 1983: An Introduction to Film, Jeff Greenstein and Jeff Strauss, UA044.003.024.00032 (Box 24)
  - EXP 55F, Fall 1982/Spring 1983: Dynamics of Human Communication, Judith Bernstein, 1982 -- 1983; UA044.003.024.00033 (Box 24)
  - EXP 55F, Fall 1979: Writing about the Arts, Pat McGilligan, UA044.003.024.00034 (Box 24)
  - EXP 55F, Fall 1978: Film Noir, Sarah Smith, UA044.003.024.00035 (Box 24)
  - EXP 55S, Fall 1974/Fall 1976/Spring 1978: Writing News for Broadcast, Les Woodruff, 1974 -- 1978; UA044.003.024.00036 (Box 24)
  - EXP 56F, Fall 1989: Screenwriting, Kevin Miller, UA044.003.024.00037 (Box 24)
  - EXP 56F, Fall 1987: On Documentary, Barry Dornfeld, UA044.003.024.00038 (Box 24)
  - EXP 56F, Fall 1986: Male and Female Images in Contemporary American Cinema, Alia Arasoughly, UA044.003.024.00039 (Box 24)
  - EXP 56F, Fall 1984: The Screenplay, Lisa McElaney, UA044.003.024.00040 (Box 24)
  - EXP 56S, Spring 1984: News Writing, Marcellus Holmes, UA044.003.024.00041 (Box 24)
  - EXP 56F, Fall 1981: Publishing Process: Books and Magazines, William McBee, UA044.003.024.00042 (Box 24)
  - EXP 56F, Fall 1980/Spring 1981: Television Production, Tony Benis, Mark Mastromatteo, 1980 -- 1981; UA044.003.024.00043 (Box 24)
  - EXP 56S, Spring 1979: Radio Production, Howard Horton, UA044.003.024.00044 (Box 24)
  - EXP 56F, Fall 1973: Television News, David Ropeik, UA044.003.024.00045 (Box 24)
  - EXP 56S, Spring 1977: Introduction to Avant Garde Film, Stephen Anker, UA044.003.024.00046 (Box 24)
  - EXP 57F, Fall 1989/Spring 1990: Film Production, George Vela, 1989 -- 1990; UA044.003.024.00047 (Box 24)
  - EXP 57F, Fall 1988: The Screenplay, Bistra Lankova, UA044.003.024.00048 (Box 24)
  - EXP 57S, Spring 1986: Politics, Media, and the News: Sorting Through the Images, Ron Kertzner and Kirk Johnson, UA044.003.024.00049 (Box 24)
  - EXP 57F, Fall 1985: The Alternative Cinema: 1920-Present, Dennis Piana, UA044.003.024.00050 (Box 24)
  - EXP 57F, Fall 1983 (EXP 58S): Introduction to Public Speaking, David Moffat, UA044.003.024.00051 (Box 24)
  - EXP 57F, Fall 1982: How the News Fits: Issues in Print Reporting, Phil Primack, UA044.003.024.00052 (Box 24)
  - EXP 57S, Spring 1979: Educational Media Materials in Health Professions, Michael Brown, UA044.003.024.00053 (Box 24)
  - EXP 57F, Fall 1977: Women Make Film, Film Make Women, Sarah Smith, UA044.003.024.00054 (Box 24)
  - EXP 58S, Spring 1985: Propaganda, Advertising, and the Mass Media in the 20th Century, David Lundberg, UA044.003.024.00055 (Box 24)
  - EXP 58F, Fall 1984: Law, Ethics, and Reporting, Ron Kertzner, UA044.003.024.00056 (Box 24)
  - EXP 58S, Spring 1984: Changing the Rules: The Impact of the News Media in the 1980s, Wendy O'Donnell, UA044.003.024.00057 (Box 24)
  - EXP 58S, Spring 1982: The New Television: Programming and Policy, Philip Miller, UA044.003.024.00058 (Box 24)
  - EXP 58F, Fall 1981: TV, Public Interest, Public Policy: Philip Miller, UA044.003.024.00059 (Box 24)
  - EXP 58F, Fall 1980/Fall 1987: Pioneer Women, Polly Welts Kaufman, UA044.003.024.00060 (Box 24)
  - EXP 58S, Spring 1979: TV Production and Management, Tony Benis, UA044.003.024.00061 (Box 24)
  - EXP 58F, Fall 1977: Introduction to Alternative Media, Howard Horton, UA044.003.024.00062 (Box 24)
  - EXP 58S, Spring 1977: Publishing Newspapers and Magazines, Phil Blampied, UA044.003.024.00063 (Box 24)
  - EXP 59S, Spring 1989: Breaking Silence: Images of Asian Americans in Film, Anita Chang and Therese On, UA044.003.024.00064 (Box 24)
  - EXP 56F, Fall 1985/Sring 1986: Inside Contemporary Music, John Harris, 1985 -- 1986; UA044.003.024.00065 (Box 24)
  - EXP 59S, Spring 1985: American Film Genres, Brian Kelly, UA044.003.024.00066 (Box 24)
  - EXP 59F, Fall 1984: The Role of TV in the Family, Irene Goodman, UA044.003.024.00067 (Box 24)
  - EXP 59S, Spring 1984: The Journalist as a Historian, Suzanne Sibs and Robert Unterberger, UA044.003.024.00068 (Box 24)
  - EXP 59F, Fall 1983: Poster Art and Propaganda 1880-1980, K. Guild Nichols, UA044.003.024.00069 (Box 24)
  - EXP 59F, Fall 1982: Community Video Production, Bonnie Symansky, UA044.003.024.00070 (Box 24)
  - EXP 59F, Fall 1980: Central America: Roots of the Crisis, James Bradford, UA044.003.024.00071 (Box 24)
  - EXP 59S, Spring 1980: Television Production, Mark Mastromatteo, UA044.003.024.00072 (Box 24)
  - EXP 59S, Spring 1969: Film Criticism, Paul Arthur, UA044.003.024.00073 (Box 24)
  - EXP 60F, Fall 1989/Fall 1992: Developmental Studies, Christopher Williams, 1989 -- 1992; UA044.003.024.00074 (Box 24)
  - EXP 60S, Spring 1985: The American Counterculture in the 1960s, Steven Adelman, UA044.003.024.00075 (Box 24)
  - EXP 60S, Spring 1983: Ancient Warfare, Jeffrey Hamilton, UA044.003.024.00076 (Box 24)
  - EXP 60S, Spring 1979: OPEC: Myths and Realities, Ahmed Jehani, UA044.003.024.00077 (Box 24)
  - EXP 60F, Fall 1977: Street Criers to Commericals, Pamela Lurito, UA044.003.024.00078 (Box 24)
  - EXP 60F, Fall 1976: Third World Women in America, Patricia Hill, UA044.003.024.00079 (Box 24)
  - EXP 60S, Spring 1976: Urban Perception, Don Brown, UA044.003.024.00080 (Box 24)
  - EXP 61F, Fall 1997: Peoples and Religions of the Silk Road: The Crossroads of the East and the West, Mariko Walter, UA044.003.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - EXP 61F, Fall 1986: Applied Politics of Women's Issues, Sue Tucker, UA044.003.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - EXP 61S, Spring 1985: Everyday Life in the Middle Ages, Joseph Callahan, UA044.003.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - EXP 61S, Spring 1984: Armenian Civilization, Krikor Maksoudian, UA044.003.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - EXP 61F, Fall 1983: Latin American Women and Issues of Development, Lynn Stephen, UA044.003.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - EXP 61S, Spring 1983: The Causes of the Iranian Revolution, Reza Kefayati, UA044.003.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - EXP 61S, Spring 1976: History of Chile and Allende, Andres Drobny, UA044.003.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - EXP 62F, Fall 1987: Armenian-Turkish Relations, Gerard Libaridian, UA044.003.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - EXP 62S, Spring 1987: Profiles in Charisma: Political Leaders in Latin America, Kevin McNamara and Stephen B. Sayre, UA044.003.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - EXP 62S, Spring 1986: Global Population Issues, Ned Hodgson, UA044.003.025.00010 (Box 25)
  - EXP 62F, Fall 1984: Islam and the Role of Women, Uzma Shakir, UA044.003.025.00011 (Box 25)
  - EXP 62S, Spring 1984: Muslim Asia in the Soviet Union, Beatrice Forbes Manz, UA044.003.025.00012 (Box 25)
  - EXP 62S, Spring 1983: Guatemala: Social Movements and Social Conflict, Beatriz Manz, UA044.003.025.00013 (Box 25)
  - EXP 62S, Spring 1979/Fall 1979/Spring 1980/Fall 1980: Influential Writing in the Mass Media, Laurence Barton, 1979 -- 1980; UA044.003.025.00014 (Box 25)
  - EXP 62F, Fall 1978: Alternative Economic Communities, John Hammock and Jeffrey Ashe, UA044.003.025.00015 (Box 25)
  - EXP 62F, Fall 1976: Industrial Archeology, Staneley Moss, UA044.003.025.00016 (Box 25)
  - EXP 62F, Fall 1975: Campaigns, Elections: ABCs, Chris Tsouros, UA044.003.025.00017 (Box 25)
  - EXP 62F, Fall 1973: Research in the Public Interest, Charles Tenney, UA044.003.025.00018 (Box 25)
  - EXP 63F, Fall 1986: Culture, Gender and Power, Emily Kearns, UA044.003.025.00019 (Box 25)
  - EXP 63F, Fall 1983: Understanding the Soviets, Igor Lukes, UA044.003.025.00020 (Box 25)
  - EXP 63F, Fall 1982: Apple PIE: Microprogramming Projects in Public Interest Engineering, Craig Decker, UA044.003.025.00021 (Box 25)
  - EXP 63F, Fall 1981: Understanding Nuclear Power, Alexander Gatzimos, UA044.003.025.00022 (Box 25)
  - EXP 63F, Fall 1980/Spring 1981: Contradictions in Reporting of U.S. Foreign Policy, Philip Martin, 1980 -- 1981; UA044.003.025.00023 (Box 25)
  - EXP 63S, Spring 1974/Fall 1974/Spring 1975/Fall 1975/Spring 1976/Fall 1976/Spring 1977/Fall 1977/Spring 1978/Summer 1978/Spring 1979/Fall1979/Spring 1980: Understanding International News, Henry Delfiner, 1974 -- 1980; UA044.003.025.00024 (Box 25)
  - EXP 63F, Fall 1973: Irish Nationalist Movements, David Cody, UA044.003.025.00025 (Box 25)
  - EXP 63F, Fall 1972: Women in History,Sherrin Wyntjes, UA044.003.025.00026 (Box 25)
  - EXP 63S, Spring 1972: Introduction to the American Legal System, Antonia Chayes, UA044.003.025.00027 (Box 25)
  - EXP 63F, Fall 1970: Politics and Peoples of S.E. Asia, Cynthia Fredrick, UA044.003.025.00028 (Box 25)
  - EXP 63S, Spring 1969: Nuclear Weapons, Reilly Atkinson III, UA044.003.025.00029 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64S, Spring 1986: Developing Countries in World Economy, Christopher Laszlo, UA044.003.025.00030 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64F, Fall 1984: American Foreign Policy Since 1945, Bradley Larschan, UA044.003.025.00031 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64F, Fall 1981: Community Energy Planning, Steven Kadish and Amy Schectman, UA044.003.025.00032 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64F, Fall 1980: Energy and the Environment, Eric Entemann, UA044.003.025.00033 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64F, Fall 1978/Fall 1979/Spring 1981: Public Policy, Energy, Ralph Chapman, 1978 -- 1981; UA044.003.025.00034 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64S, Spring 1977: Introduction to Radical Economics, Philip Aranow, UA044.003.025.00035 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64F, Fall 1976: Political Psychology, David Rothberg, UA044.003.025.00036 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64F, Fall 1975: Devel, Underdevel, and the Third World, Richard Samuels and Ricardo Stein, UA044.003.025.00037 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64S, Spring 1975: Politics and Environmental Protection, Alan Patterson, UA044.003.025.00038 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64S, Spring 1974/Fall 1974: Theory and Practice of Non-Violence, Paula Raymon and Robert Read, UA044.003.025.00039 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64F, Fall 1973: Politics of Liberation, Larry Ahart, UA044.003.025.00040 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64S, Spring 1973: Prisons, Joseph Centorino, UA044.003.025.00041 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64S, Spring 1972: Law of Criminal Procedure II, Gerald Goodstein, UA044.003.025.00042 (Box 25)
  - EXP 64S, Spring 1970 (EXP 64F, Fall 1970/Fall 1971): Ancient Egyptian Civilization, Alex Kaczmarczyk, 1970 -- 1971; UA044.003.025.00043 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1989: World Militarization, Sherman Teichman, UA044.003.025.00044 (Box 25)
  - EXP F65, Fall 1988: Drugs, National Security, and U.S. Public Policy, Sherman Teichman, UA044.003.025.00045 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1988: The Economy of Death and Dependence: Drugs, Money, and Politics, Sherman Teichman, UA044.003.025.00046 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1987: U.S. Foreign Policy and Secrecy, Sherman Teichman, UA044.003.025.00047 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1986: The West Bank and Gaza: 20 Years of Israeli Control, Sherman Teichman, UA044.003.025.00048 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1985: Anarchism and the Law, Donna Turley, UA044.003.025.00049 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1983: Northern Ireland, David Buckley, UA044.003.025.00050 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1982: Local Solutions to National Problems, Mona Hochberg and Ron Shegda, UA044.003.025.00051 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65S, Spring 1981: International Aspects of Journalism, Henry Delfiner, UA044.003.025.00052 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1980: Radical Politics and the Environment, Donald Falk, UA044.003.025.00053 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65S, Spring 1980: Daily Life in Nazi Germany, Kelly Cameron and Sam Goodfellow, UA044.003.025.00054 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65S, Spring 1979: The Historical Development of the Form of the City, Michael Bernard, UA044.003.025.00055 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65S, Spring 1978/Fall 1978: How to Be Politically Effective, Jerome Grossman, UA044.003.025.00056 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1976: Community and Social Development, Paula Rayman, UA044.003.025.00057 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65S, Spring 1976: Ancient Egypt, Alex Kaczmarczyk, UA044.003.025.00058 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1975: Studio in Community Development, James Carras and Andrew Safran, UA044.003.025.00059 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1974: Community Organization in Third World Countries, Arthur and Brenda Powers, UA044.003.025.00060 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65S, Spring 1974: Theories of Democracy, Stephen Slaner, UA044.003.025.00061 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65S, Spring 1973: History and Psychology of the Holocaust, Roy Doliner and Robin Gowa, UA044.003.025.00062 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65F, Fall 1973: Rebirth of Jewish Nationalism 1789-1948, Mitchell Knisbacher, UA044.003.025.00063 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65S, Spring 1972: Post-1967 Greater Israel, Uri Davis, UA044.003.025.00064 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65S, Spring 1971: The Heritage of Babylon, Alex Kaczmarczyk, UA044.003.025.00065 (Box 25)
  - EXP 65S, Spring 1969/Spring 1970: The Draft: Military Conscription in the U.S.A., H.A. Bedau, 1969 -- 1970; UA044.003.025.00066 (Box 25)
  - EXP 66S, Spring 1986: Legal Controls of International Use of Force, Marc Weller, UA044.003.025.00067 (Box 25)
  - EXP 66S, Spring 1985: Law and Society in the Middle East, Nagla Nassar, UA044.003.025.00068 (Box 25)
  - EXP 66S, Spring 1984: The American Worker in the Twentieth Century, David Goldberg, UA044.003.025.00069 (Box 25)
  - EXP 66F, Fall 1981: History of Work and Workers in the U.S., Mark Erlich, UA044.003.025.00070 (Box 25)
  - EXP 66S, Spring 1981: Implications of Marxism in the Third World, Filipe Noguera, UA044.003.025.00071 (Box 25)
  - EXP 66F, Fall 1978: Anarchism, Marty Blatt, UA044.003.025.00072 (Box 25)
  - EXP 66F, Fall 1977: Political Economy of Socialism, Philip Aranow, UA044.003.025.00073 (Box 25)
  - EXP 66S, Spring 1977: Arms Sales and Arms Control, Rip Fisher and Bill Fish, UA044.003.025.00074 (Box 25)
  - EXP 66S, Spring 1976: The Family in History, Margo Horn, UA044.003.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - EXP 66S, Spring 1975: City Planning and Strategies: Boston, James Carras, UA044.003.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - EXP 66S, Spring 1973/Fall 1973: Zionism Revisited, Martin Blatt, UA044.003.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - EXP 66F, Fall 1971: West-European Left, James Kaplan, UA044.003.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - EXP 66S, Spring 1971: The Cuban Revolutio, Mark Freidman, George Mastellone, UA044.003.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - EXP 66S, Spring 1970: Introductory History of Radicalism in the U.S., Steven Miller, UA044.003.026.00006 (Box 26)
  - EXP 66S, Spring 1968: The New Left, Saul Slapikoff, UA044.003.026.00007 (Box 26)
  - EXP 67S, Spring 1990: Urbanization and Urban Development in Developing Countries, Charles Setchell, UA044.003.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - EXP 67F, Fall 1989: Conflict in the Middle East, Denis Sullivan, UA044.003.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - EXP 67S, Spring 1989: Migration, Return, and Social Change, Ayse Berkin, UA044.003.026.00010 (Box 26)
  - EXP 67S, Spring 1987: Political Geography, Adam Garth, UA044.003.026.00011 (Box 26)
  - EXP 67F, Fall 1985/Spring 1986: The Political Economy of Third World Debt Crisis, Diane Davis, 1985 -- 1986; UA044.003.026.00012 (Box 26)
  - EXP 67S, Spring 1985: Foreign Affairs and the U.S. Constitution, Bradley Larschan, UA044.003.026.00013 (Box 26)
  - EXP 67S, Spring 1979: American Jewish History, Robert Shapiro, UA044.003.026.00014 (Box 26)
  - EXP 67F, Fall 1977/Fall 1978/Fall 1979/Fall 1980/Fall 1982: Neighborhood Preservation and Development in Boston, James Carras, 1977 -- 1982; UA044.003.026.00015 (Box 26)
  - EXP 67S, Spring 1977: Understanding the Interdependence of Global Society, Mohammed Islam, UA044.003.026.00016 (Box 26)
  - EXP 67S, Spring 1976: Sport and International Politics, David Kanin, UA044.003.026.00017 (Box 26)
  - EXP 68S, Spring 1986: Negotiation, Michael Landry and Mark Ferri, UA044.003.026.00018 (Box 26)
  - EXP 68S, Spring 1985: Introduction to Policy and Strategy, Paul Johnson, UA044.003.026.00019 (Box 26)
  - EXP 68S, Spring 1984: Are You Now or Have You Ever Been, Steve Adelman and Helene Aronson, UA044.003.026.00020 (Box 26)
  - EXP 68F, Fall 1978: Organized Crime (EXP 69S, Spring 1979: The Mafia), Steven Miller, 1978 -- 1979; UA044.003.026.00021 (Box 26)
  - EXP 68S, Spring 1978: Zionists versus Palestinians, Gabriel Marshi, UA044.003.026.00022 (Box 26)
  - EXP 68F, Fall 1976: American Political Trials, Carol Green, UA044.003.026.00023 (Box 26)
  - EXP 68S, Spring 1976: Intermediate Computer Applications, Ronald Wang and Steven D'Alessio, UA044.003.026.00024 (Box 26)